<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>$HOME</title>
    <link>https://jreisinger.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on $HOME</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jreisinger.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jreisinger.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jreisinger.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am interested in universal machines for information storage and manipulation :-). Among other things. To be a bit more specific, I dabble in systems administration, security and programming. I log some of the technical activities I should do. I try to be nice to people (it&amp;rsquo;s not an easy task). I like sports, books and languages.
Some of my (free time) software projects:
 quotes Profesia Jobs App::Monport lsfat checkprocs  Pearls I found on the Internet:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://jreisinger.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jreisinger.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>I have been doing IT stuff for companies of varied sizes and types for 10+ years. My experience is mainly in systems administration (SRE) and IT security. I have touched several infrastructures and done quite some programming or scripting. I try to stay on top of new technologies and practices and use them when/where appropriate. I am not bad at managing smaller projects and teams. I can communicate well with technical and non-technical folks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://jreisinger.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jreisinger.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Some of my (free time) software projects:
 quotes Profesia Jobs App::Monport lsfat checkprocs  Pearls I found on the Internet:
 The saddest phone in Berlin How to daemonize a process Larry Wall on Perl, religion, and&amp;hellip; What problems to solve xkcd - Lisp  Buy me stuff if you want to make me happy :-). I take photos from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>